Clara E. Sipprell Papers
Clara E. Sipprell Papers
- Negatives and proof prints
  - Konenkov, Sergei, with god-daughter Nina
    - Negatives (Box FB120)
    - Negatives (Box FB158)
  - Konenkov, Sergei, and Einstein sculptures
    - Negatives (Box FB034)
  - Konenkov, Sergei, bust of lady
    - Negatives (Box FB034)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Konenkov, Sergei, bust of professor's wife
    - Negatives (Box FB035)
  - Konenkov, Sergei, sculptures, Jan 1930
    See also Photographs: Paganini by Konenkov.
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box 64)
    - Negatives (Box FB034)
    - Negatives (Box FB035)
    - Negatives (Box FB157)
    - Negatives (Box FB199)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Koreneva, [Lydia] as Kateriva
    - Negatives (Box FB189)
  - Kortschak, Mr. Hugo
    - Negatives (Box FB035)
    - Negatives (Box FB120)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Koussevitsky, Sergei
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB121)
  - Kouwenhoven, Mrs. John A.
    - Negatives (Box FB121)
  - Krasner, Louis
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB158)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Krusen, Miss Gertrude, 1956
    - Negatives (Box FB035)
  - Kyle, Mrs. A.W.W., 1958
    - Negatives (Box FB035)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Kyle, Mrs. A.W.W. (niece), 1959
    - Negatives (Box FB035)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - LaFleur, Old Dan
    - Negatives (Box 52)
  - Lakeway, Ruth
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB035)
    - Negatives (Box FB158)
  - Lamb, Helen (daughter of Mrs. Albert R. Lamb)
    - Negatives (Box FB121)
  - Lanbendorfer, ----, 1955
    - Negatives (Box FB035)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Lanbendorfer, Mrs. Elvia, 1958
    - Negatives (Box FB035)
  - Lanbendorfer, Pamela (granddaughter of Vis)
    - Negatives (Box FB035)
  - Lancaster, Mrs. Charles (Manchester)
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB035)
    - Negatives (Box FB158)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Landscape (Georgia, Sea Island, Mrs. M. Parish etc., and Marshes of Glynn, plantation)
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB154)
  - Landscapes
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box 64)
    - Negatives (Box FB121)
    - Negatives (Box FB158)
    - Negatives (Box FB159)
    - Negatives (Box FB160)
    - Negatives (Box FB199)
    - Negatives (Box FB204)
  - Landscapes and trees
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box 64)
    - Negatives (Box FB160)
    - Negatives (Box FB199)
  - Landscapes etc.
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB035)
    - Negatives (Box FB159)
    - Negatives (Box FB199)
    - Negatives (Box FB160)
    - Negatives (Box FB204)
  - Landscapes west
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB196)
    - Negatives (Box FB121)
    - Negatives (Box FB122)
    - Negatives (Box FB160)
    - Negatives (Box FB199)
  - Lane, Captain Robert W.
    - Negatives (Box FB122)
  - Langdon, Katherine (niece of Mrs. Duane L. Bliss)
    - Negatives (Box FB035)
  - [Lanier?] Lenier, Mrs. Sidney and grandchild
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB122)
    - Negatives (Box FB160)
  - Lanzetta, Mr.
    - Negatives (Box FB036)
  - Lardin, Mrs. Harry E. (388 Merrimon Ave. Asheville, NC Elaine, Eddy)
    - Negatives (Box FB036)
  - Lashkoff, Nicolas
    - Negatives (Box FB122)
  - Lashkoff, Nicolas (daughter)
    - Negatives (Box FB036)
  - Lathrop, John Howland
    - Negatives (Box FB122)
  - Lathrop, William (Painter, New Hope, PA)
    - Negatives (Box FB189)
  - Lauds Capes, French Canada [empty folder]
  - Laughly, Miss E.
    - Glass plate negative (Box 69-01)
  - Lautz, Joanne
    - Glass plate negative (Box 69-01)
  - Lawrence, Mr. and Mrs. H.B., 1954
    - Negatives (Box FB122)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Lawton, Dr. Shailer [Shaker?]
    - Negatives (Box FB122)
  - Leavey, General and Mrs. E.H., 1959
    - Negatives (Box FB036)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Leavitt, Mrs. Brooks
    - Negatives (Box FB122)
  - Lebherz, Mr. Richard, 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB036)
  - Lee, Mr. Robert (son, Manchester)
    - Negatives (Box FB036)
  - Leeds, Tony
    - Negatives (Box FB036)
  - Lees, Mr. and Mrs. Allen T., 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB036)
  - Leggett, Mrs. Albert C. [empty folder]
  - Lemke, Antje, 1967; 1970
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB036)
    - Negatives (Box FB160)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Leonard Jr., Mrs. Robert J. (Dorset), 1955
    - Negatives (Box FB122)
  - Leonard, Mrs. Richard B.
    - Negatives (Box FB122)
  - Leonard, Richard, 1946
    - Negatives (Box FB123)
  - Leonard, Ricky
    - Negatives (Box FB036)
  - Lesh, Mrs. H. Frederick, 1956
    - Negatives (Box FB036)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Levene, Mr. Harry and family
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB036)
    - Negatives (Box FB160)
  - Levene, Mrs. Harry, 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB036)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Levene, Mrs. Harry
    - Negatives (Box FB123)
  - Levison, J.J.
    - Negatives (Box FB123)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Lewar, Katherine (son)
    - Negatives (Box FB123)
  - Lewis, Mrs. Fulton
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB036)
    - Negatives (Box FB199)
  - Lewis, Larry D., 1959
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB036)
    - Negatives (Box FB160)
  - Lewis, Mrs. M.P.
    - Negatives (Box FB123)
  - Lieb, Charles, 1966
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB036)
  - Lieb, Maron, 1966
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB036)
    - Negatives (Box FB160)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Lillie, John
    - Negatives (Box FB123)
  - Limrick, Rachel, 1961
    - Negatives (Box FB037)
  - Lincoln School
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB161)
  - Linderberg, Sigrid
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB037)
    - Negatives (Box FB160)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Linderberg, Sigrid, and Dorothy Newel, 1945-1947
    - Negatives (Box FB123)
  - Linn, Ann H.
    - Negatives (Box FB199)
    - Negatives (Box 52)
  - Liss, Mrs. Herman
    - Negatives (Box FB037)
  - List, Alison (granddaughter of Mrs. James Glenn)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - List, Carol
    - Negatives (Box FB037)
    - Negatives (Box FB161)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
    - Negatives (Box 52)
  - List, Eugene, 1960
    - Negatives (Box FB037)
  - Little, Mr. Albert (Hartford, Conn,)
    - Negatives (Box FB189)
  - Little, Susan (daughter of Mrs. Edward H. Little, Hartford, CT)
    - Negatives (Box FB037)
  - Livingston, Mrs. Francis S. (268 Chestnut Street, Asheville, NC)
    - Negatives (Box FB123)
  - Llitge, Professor and Mrs. H. Karl and Carol's sister Sally (East Millstone, NJ)
    - Negatives (Box FB123)
  - Lloyd, Anne
    - Negatives (Box FB037)
  - Lorizeaux, Mr. and Mrs. J.H. and 4 children
    - Negatives (Box FB123)
  - Lorizeaux, Mr. Harold J.
    - Negatives (Box FB123)
    - Negatives (Box FB124)
  - Loutrel, C.F. and baby, daughter, Mrs. P.P. Parker
    - Negatives (Box FB037)
  - Lovejoy, Mrs. (twins)
    - Negatives (Box FB124)
  - Lovejoy, Mr. and Mrs. Henry S. and David
    - Negatives (Box FB124)
  - Lovejoy, Lindsay
    - Negatives (Box FB037)
  - Lovett, Mrs. Robert F. and family
    - Negatives (Box FB037)
  - Low, Ilyse, 1958
    - Negatives (Box FB037)
  - Lowery, Mrs. James and baby, 1964
    - Glass plate negative (Box 69-01)
    - Negatives (Box FB037)
    - Negatives (Box FB124)
  - Lucione, Luigi
    - Negatives (Box 52)
  - Ludwig, Emil
    - Negatives (Box 52)
  - Lugalls, Mrs. Jean, 1959
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB037)
    - Negatives (Box FB161)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Lutge, Rev. H. Carl
    - Glass plate negative (broken) (Box 69-01)
  - Luzhsky, V.V. [Vasily Vasilyevich] (Moscow Art Theatre)
    See also Moscow Art Theatre, Luzhsky, Katcholoff.
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB189)
    - Negatives (Box FB199)
  - [Luzhsky?] Lushsky, Madame
    - Negatives (Box FB189)
  - Lynch, Father (White River Junction)
    - Negatives (Box FB125)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Lynch, Miss Nellie, 1956
    - Negatives (Box FB037)
  - Lyon, Mrs. Albert (Peru, VT)
    - Negatives (Box FB125)
  - Lyons, Mrs. A.B. (Kathy Brua), 1970
    - Negatives (Box FB037)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - M.J.
    - Negatives (Box FB125)
  - Mackay, Dr. and Mrs. (Burlington, VT)
    - Negatives (Box FB037)
  - Macy, Herman
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Macy, Mrs. Herman
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB037)
    - Negatives (Box FB161)
  - Maduro, [Nicolás?]
    - Negatives (Box FB038)
  - Mahood, 1966
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB038)
    - Negatives (Box FB161)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Malick, Dr. Jean
    - Negatives (Box FB125)
  - Malone, Mrs. Charles B. (granddaughter, Brier Patch)
    - Negatives (Box FB038)
  - Maloney, Francis P., 1959
    - Negatives (Box FB038)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Maloney, Mrs. Frances and children, 1959
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB038)
    - Negatives (Box FB161)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Mamov, ----
    - Glass plate negative (Box 69-01)
  - Manchester Center Church, Vermont
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB125)
    - Negatives (Box FB182)
  - Manchester, VT studio
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB182)
  - Manhattanville Nursery
    - Glass plate negative (Box 69-01)
  - Manheim, Martha (Mrs. Paul Manheim), 1936
    - Negatives (Box FB125)
  - Manheim, Paul and family, 1938
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB125)
    - Negatives (Box FB161)
  - Mann, ---- (group and baby), 1956
    - Negatives (Box FB038)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Mannheim, Mrs. Paul, 1937
    - Negatives (Box FB125)
  - Mannheim, Mrs. Paul (children)
    - Negatives (Box FB038)
  - Mansfield, ----
    - Negatives (Box FB125)
  - Mantignoni, Margaret [empty folder], 1955
  - Mareuche, Countess du
    - Negatives (Box FB038)
  - Markham, Edwin
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB125)
    - Negatives (Box FB126)
    - Negatives (Box FB161)
  - Marmalt, Mrs. Charles L. and two daughters
    - Negatives (Box FB189)
  - Marsh, Mrs. John L., 1944
    - Negatives (Box FB126)
  - Martin, Tom, 1966
    - Negatives (Box FB038)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Martinelli, Giovanni, 1944
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB038)
    - Negatives (Box FB161)
  - Marvin, Mrs. E.M. (Ronnie Beth)
    - Negatives (Box FB126)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Masten, Helen
    - Negatives (Box FB038)
  - Masten, Miss Bess
    - Negatives (Box FB038)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Master, Mrs. John R.C.
    - Negatives (Box FB126)
  - Master, Mrs. W.H. (94 years old, daughter Bess), 1960
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives (Box FB038)
    - Negatives (Box FB161)
  - Mattisori, Margaret (daughter of Mrs. N.D. Mattisori)
    - Negatives (Box FB126)
  - Maury, Lois K.
    - Negatives (Box 52)
    - Negatives, 1944 (Box FB038)
    - Negatives (Box FB161)
  - Maury, Lois K. (Keels Wedding and Lida Kellogg)
    See also [Kellogg], Lida and Lois [Maury] in the garden.
    - Negatives (Box FB038)
  - Maury, Richard
    - Negatives (Box FB039)
    - Negatives, 1944 (Box FB126)
  - Maury, Mrs. Richard (daughter), at Linn Adams' christening
    See also Adams-Linn, Mrs. John (Mrs. Richard Maury).
    - Negatives (Box FB126)
  - Mawer, Mrs. Irving (709 College Street, Beloit, WI.)
    - Negatives (Box FB126)
  - Maxwell, Mrs. Jean, 1963
    - Negatives (Box FB039)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - May, Janine
    - Negatives (Box FB039)
  - Mayberry, ----
    - Negatives (Box FB039)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Mayberry, Mrs. D.W. (2 children), 1958
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB039)
    - Negatives (Box FB161)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Mayer, Elsa (daughter of Mr. Leo Mayer)
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB039)
    - Negatives (Box FB161)
  - McClellan, Dr. William (Washington, DC)
    - Negatives (Box FB126)
  - McConnell, Mrs. James E. (garden, 84 Abbey Road, Manhasset), 1938
    - Negatives (Box FB126)
  - McCormick, Eleanor, 1941
    - Negatives (Box FB039)
  - McCormick, Eleanor (nephew)
    - Negatives (Box FB126)
  - McCormick, John Jr., 1958
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB039)
    - Negatives (Box FB161)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - McCormick, Parker (Mrs. John Fried?)
    - Negatives (Box FB127)
  - McCormick, Roxanne, bride
    - Negatives (Box FB039)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - McCormick, Roxanne (daughter of Mr. & Mrs. John McCormick, 21 years old)
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives, 1961 (Box FB039)
    - Negatives (Box FB161)
    - Proof prints, 1961 (Box 79)
  - McCoy, Lawrence
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - McCoy, Mrs Lawrence
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - McCrady, Grace
    See also Gade, August and family, and sister of Grace McCrady.
    - Negatives (Box FB127)
  - McCrea, Mary
    - Negatives (Box FB039)
  - McDonald, Mr. Frederick, 1956
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB039)
    - Negatives (Box FB161)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - McGreal, Elizabeth Yates with Bill, 1956
    - Negatives (Box FB039)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - McGreal, Elizabeth (house)
    - Negatives (Box FB039)
  - [McGreal] Yates, Elizabeth, 1967
    - Negatives (Box FB070)
  - McGreal, Elizabeth Yates
    - Negatives (Box FB070)
  - McGreal, William, 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB039)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - McGuire, Miss Ruth
    - Negatives (Box FB039)
  - McKeel, ----
    - Negatives (Box FB127)
  - McKeichie, ----
    - Negatives (Box FB039)
  - McNown, Mrs. W.K. and children
    - Negatives (Box FB039)
  - McPherson, Mrs. James G. (Saginaw), 1939
    - Negatives (Box FB127)
  - Meacham, Alfred B.
    - Negatives (Box FB127)
  - Meacham, Mrs. Standish and son Standy
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB040)
    - Negatives (Box FB161)
  - Mechlin, Lelia
    - Negatives (Box FB040)
  - Mehta, Hansa
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB040)
    - Negatives (Box FB127)
    - Negatives (Box FB161)
    - Negatives (Box FB190)
  - Melville, Carey E., Prof. and Mrs. (Worcester, MA)
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB040)
    - Negatives (Box FB161)
  - Merill, Mrs. Keith (children Keith, Rosemary, Jean; Avalon), 1933
    - Negatives (Box FB127)
  - Merrill, Keith
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB040)
    - Negatives (Box FB161)
  - Merrill, Keith (children)
    - Negatives (Box FB040)
  - Mesanova, Madame George Alla
    - Negatives (Box FB040)
  - Mestrovic, Ivan
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB161)
  - Metcalf, Mrs. S.L., 1960
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB040)
    - Negatives (Box FB161)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Mexico, 1931
    - Negatives (Box FB041)
    - Negatives (Box FB161)
    - Negatives (Box 53)
  - Mexico: Campistata [Campostela?]
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB127)
    - Negatives (Box FB162)
  - Mexico: Chat Park with stream, Pals Opara Lake
    - Negatives (Box FB127)
  - Mexico: Contreras, 1931
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB041)
    - Negatives (Box FB162)
  - Mexico: Nazat
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB041)
    - Negatives (Box FB162)
  - Mexico: Oaxaca
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB041)
    - Negatives (Box FB042)
    - Negatives (Box FB162)
  - Mexico: Pátzcuaro
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB042)
    - Negatives (Box FB162)
    - Negatives (Box FB168)
  - Mexico: Tepic
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB042)
    - Negatives (Box FB043)
    - Negatives (Box FB162)
  - Mexico: Uruapan
    - Negatives (Box FB043)
  - Mexico: Xochimilco, Chinampa "Floating Gardens", 1931
    - Negatives (Box FB043)
  - Mexico: selections from
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB162)
  - Mexico City
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB041)
    - Negatives (Box FB162)
  - Middlebury College (Vermont)
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB163)
  - Middlebury College church
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB162)
  - Miller, Mrs. Edward, 1964
    - Negatives (Box FB043)
  - Miller, Dr. Gerrit
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB199)
    - Negatives (Box FB163)
  - Miller, Hadan
    - Negatives (Box FB128)
  - Miller, Hadan (granddaughter)
    - Negatives (Box FB128)
  - Miller, Mrs. Harlan, still life, 1954-1955
    - Negatives (Box FB128)
  - Miller, Rachel, 1957
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB043)
    - Negatives (Box FB163)
    - Proof prints (Box 79)
  - Milles, Carl
    - Negatives (Box FB128)
  - Mills, Maury Post
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB163)
  - Mills, Mr. and Mrs. Richard and baby
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB043)
    - Negatives (Box FB163)
  - Mitchell, Rev. Miss Frederica, 1960
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB043)
    - Negatives (Box FB163)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Moffitt, Mr. & Mrs. Walter (some in Florida)
    - Negatives (Box FB043)
    - Negatives (Box FB044)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Morgan, Sherley (eldest son)
    - Negatives (Box FB044)
  - Monkel, Fifi (Mrs. William Monkel's daughter)
    - Negatives (Box FB128)
  - Monroe, Mrs. Adair (daughter)
    - Negatives (Box FB044)
  - Montague, Mrs. James, 1969
    - Negatives (Box FB044)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Montague, James, 1963
    - Negatives (Box FB044)
  - Montenegro landscape
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB044)
    - Negatives (Box FB163)
  - Montenegro type
    - Negatives (Box FB044)
  - Montignani, Mrs. J., 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB044)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Moore, Annie
    - Negatives (Box FB044)
  - Moore, Mrs. H.C. (daughter/Mrs. Neese's granddaughter, 1834 Strong Ave. Beloit, WI)
    - Negatives (Box FB128)
  - Moore, Richard L. Jr. (Chattanooga, TN), 1968
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB044)
    - Negatives (Box FB164)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Moore, Winnie, 1967
    - Negatives (Box FB044)
    - Negatives (Box FB164)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Morain Park, Bear Lake, 1931
    - Negatives (Box FB044)
    - Negatives (Box FB190)
  - Morgan, Diana
    - Negatives (Box FB045)
  - Morgan, Mrs. (son)
    - Negatives (Box FB045)
  - Morgan, Mrs. George (Saginaw), 1939-1940
    - Negatives (Box FB045)
  - Morgan, Richard
    - Negatives (Box FB045)
  - Morgan, Mrs. Sherley, Richard (Mr. M. and grandchildren), 1965
    - Negatives (Box FB045)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Morrison, Dr. William W., 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB045)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Morrison, Mrs.
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB045)
    - Negatives (Box FB164)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Morton, David
    - Negatives (Box FB045)
  - Morton, Mrs. W.G. and Mrs. Green, 1965
    - Negatives (Box FB190)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Moscow Art Theatre, 1955
    See also Bulgakoff, [Mikhail?], Evrenoff, ----, Luzhsky, V.V., and Moskvin, Ivan, all of whom were involved with the Theatre. There are also related items in Photographs.
    - Negatives (Box FB190)
    - Negatives (Box FB199)
    - Negatives (Box FB164)
    - Negatives (Box 53)
  - Moscow Art [Theatre] (Bulgakoff, Moskina, Boris)
    - Negatives (Box FB190)
  - Moscow Art Theatre, Luzhsky, Katcholoff
    - Negatives (Box FB190)
  - Moscow Art Theatre, Tarasaine?
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB190)
    - Negatives (Box FB199)
  - Moskvin, Ivan (Moscow Art Theatre)
    - Negatives (Box 61)
    - Negatives (Box FB190)
  - Moskvin, Ivan as "Luka" and "Boris"
    - Negatives (Box FB190)
  - Muller, Dr. Haus and family
    - Negatives (Box FB128)
  - Muller, Haus
    - Negatives (Box FB045)
  - Muller, Inez and baby
    - Negatives (Box FB045)
  - Munson, Mrs.
    - Negatives (Box FB128)
  - Murphy, Mr. John H.
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB045)
    - Negatives (Box FB046)
    - Negatives (Box FB190)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Murray, Mr. George Welwood, 1941
    - Negatives (Box FB046)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Myers, Mr. and Mrs. Walter A.
    - Negatives (Box FB128)
  - Nagashoff, Boris
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB128)
  - Nathan, Mrs., 1969
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB046)
  - Naugle, Mrs. A.T.
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB190)
  - Naumberg, E.
    - Negatives (Box FB191)
  - Negros, Georgia
    - Negatives (Box FB128)
  - Nelson, ----, 1937
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB046)
  - [Nersoyan], Bishop Tiran
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB177)
  - New Jersey churches
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB191)
  - New York from my window, Morningside Drive
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB046)
    - Negatives (Box FB174)
    - Negatives (Box FB200)
  - New York landscape and portrait of old man
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB046)
    - Negatives (Box FB165)
    - Negatives (Box FB169)
    - Negatives (Box FB200)
  - New York City
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box FB046)
    - Negatives (Box FB128)
    - Negatives (Box FB129)
    - Negatives (Box FB164)
    - Negatives (Box FB165)
    - Negatives (Box FB191)
    - Negatives (Box FB196)
    - Negatives (Box FB200)
  - New York Harbor
    - Negatives (Box FB129)
  - Newell, Dorothy, 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB046)
    - Negatives (Box FB129)
  - Newton, Dr. and Mrs. (Krumdieck), 1962
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box FB046)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Ney, Paul
    - Negatives (Box FB129)
  - Nichols, ---- (Thetford)
    - Negatives (Box FB129)
  - Nichols, Mrs. George
    - Negatives (Box FB046)
  - Nielson, Miss Sarah
    - Negatives (Box FB129)
  - Niendorff, Mrs. A.F. (sons Walter and Carl), 1955
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - [Nikhilananda, Swami?] Nikelilanda, Sevaine
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box FB046)
    - Negatives (Box FB173)
  - Nikhilananda, Swami
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box FB046)
    - Negatives (Box FB129)
    - Negatives (Box FB165)
  - Nix, Mrs. Robert D., 1959
    - Negatives (Box FB046)
  - Noguchi, Isamu, 1955
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box FB046)
    - Negatives (Box FB167)
  - Norburn, Mrs. Charles Sr. (mother of Dr. Charles Norburn)
    - Negatives (Box FB131)
  - Norburn, Dr. Charles (Biltmore Forest, P.O Box 5216) and also group
    - Negatives (Box FB131)
  - Norburn, Mrs. Russel (54 Hilltop Rd. Asheville, NC), Russell Lee Jr., "Cherie"
    - Negatives (Box FB131)
  - North Carolina
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB047)
    - Negatives (Box FB167)
    - Negatives (Box FB200)
  - Nudes
    - Glass plate negative (Box 69-01)
    - Glass plate negative (Box 69-01)
  - Nutting, Adalaide
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box FB047)
    - Negatives (Box FB167)
  - Oates, Springle
    - Negatives (Box FB047)
  - Oestreich, Mr. & Mrs. George, 1958
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box FB047)
    - Negatives (Box FB167)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Old Bill
    - Glass plate negative (Box 69-01)
    - Negatives (Box FB047)
  - Old man
    - Glass plate negative (Box 69-01)
  - Old tree north of summit
    - Negatives (Box FB191)
  - Olmstead, Harold, 1958
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box FB047)
    - Negatives (Box FB167)
  - Olmsted, Janice
    - Negatives (Box FB047)
  - Olmsted, John
    - Negatives (Box FB047)
  - Olmsted, Miss
    - Negatives (Box FB047)
  - Oppenheim, Mrs., and Miss Schwartz
    - Negatives (Box FB047)
  - Oracle at Camp Hanourn
    - Glass plate negative (Box 69-01)
  - Orcutt, Mrs. Brent
    - Negatives (Box FB047)
    - Negatives, 1940 (Box FB131)